<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<articles>
	<article>
        <title>Cosmetology</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<h1>Cosmetology</h1>
<img src='benefit_mr'/><br>
♞ A passionate kiss will face 34 muscles tense, make the skin more smooth, the blood supply of the facial skin, increased by 30% , helps improve facial muscle tissue, play the role of beauty.
            ]]></text>
    </article>

	<article>
        <title>Protect Teeth</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<h1>Protect Teeth</h1>
<img src='benefit_hc'/><br>
♞ Increased salivation kiss process. Saliva contains calcium and trace elements, after being absorbed by the enamel can prevent tooth decay; kissing process, saliva pH is neutral, but also can prevent dental disease. Saliva natural antibiotic - enzymes can be controlled by the number of bacteria in the mouth. Saliva also useful for wound healing growth genes.
            ]]></text>
    </article>

	<article>
        <title>Immunity</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<h1>Immunity</h1>
<img src='benefit_my'/><br>
♞ Our saliva contains large amounts of bacteria. 20% of bacteria varies. Kissing object in the mouth, bacteria once added to the others, these microorganisms will produce different responses. So can stimulate a person's immune system to produce specific antibodies.
            ]]></text>
    </article>
	
	<article>
        <title>Lose Weight</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<h1>Lose Weight</h1>
<img src='benefit_jf'/><br>
♞ Kissing a minute, can consume 26 calories. Kiss male heartbeat can be increased to 110 beats per minute, heart rate can be increased to 108 females per minute, and then the blood circulation. These changes mobilize the body's cells fuel - adenosine triphosphate easily burn fat. Up to French kiss calories consumed.
            ]]></text>
    </article>
	
	<article>
        <title>Relieve Pain</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<h1>Relieve Pain</h1>
<img src='benefit_zt'/><br>
♞ The more passionate kiss, the body will secrete more endorphins. Endorphin hormone is a good anesthetic, a hormone produced by kissing can achieve the effect of a painkiller.
            ]]></text>
    </article>
	
	<article>
        <title>Decompression</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<h1>Decompression</h1>
<img src='benefit_jy'/><br>
♞ Adrenocorticotropic hormone or a stress hormone, since it can prevent the formation of kissing adrenocorticotropic hormone, so kissing can effectively help you calm down from the tense mood, like kissing people are usually optimistic, but also because of this reason. Kissing three times a day can make you 24 hours are in a romantic and pleasant atmosphere.
            ]]></text>
    </article>
	
	<article>
        <title>Health</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<h1>Health</h1>
<img src='benefit_jk'/><br>
♞ 1、Cardiovascular more stable, lower blood pressure, lower cholesterol. Kiss will make people heart rate, blood circulation improves the body carefree oxygen levels. Adrenal hormones also cause high blood pressure, high cholesterol, insomnia, muscle atrophy, and the culprit, but kissing can prevent the formation of adrenal hormones.<br>
♞ 2、Exercise lung capacity. We often take a deep breath before the kiss, and then slowly exhaled air kiss during the alveoli do not consciously make a deep breath, improves oxygen supply to the alveoli, exercise vital capacity.<br>
♞ 3、Reduce the risk of stomach problems, blood disease odds. Those who regularly kissing chance in the stomach, bladder and blood systems of illness will be smaller.
            ]]></text>
    </article>
 </articles>