<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<articles>
	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Practice-Kissing -->
        <title>Practice Kissing</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<img src='training_lxjw_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Find a ripe piece of soft fruit, such as a plum, apricot, or mango. These fruits are soft and taste good.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_lxjw_02'/><br/>
<big>2　</big>Bite a small, mouth-sized hole in the fruit.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_lxjw_03'/><br/>
<big>3　</big>Use this as the mouth that you'll practice kissing with.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_lxjw_04'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>Kiss the fruit mouth gently. Try to establish a rhythm. Kiss the top part of the "mouth," and then the bottom part of the "mouth." For goodness' sake, don't eat your kissing partner.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_lxjw_05'/><br/>
<big>5　</big>Use your tongue by gently pushing it into the flesh of the fruit. Remember to use the tongue sparingly. You don't want to overdo it with the tongue.<br/><br/>
            ]]></text>
    </article>
    

	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Kiss-Someone-for-the-First-Time -->
        <title>Prepare to Kiss</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<img src='training_zbjw_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Freshen your breath. Having fresh, kissable breath is a major component of having a knockout first kiss. Make sure that you have brushed your teeth and used mouthwash some time before the kiss, or that you chewed minty gum or sucked on a breath mint before the kiss. You can do this an hour or so before -- you don't want your breath to be too minty or it will look like you tried a little too hard to get ready for the kiss.
<p>　● If you had dinner or ate before the kiss, you should avoid ordering any foods that are heavy in garlic, onions, or any intense spices.</p>

<img src='training_zbjw_02'/><br/>
<big>2　</big>Set the mood. It's important to share your first kiss in an intimate or romantic atmosphere. Your first kiss may be something you remember for the rest of your lives, so you should make it special. You don't have to bring out a thousand candles or serenade the person, but you should pick the ideal time and place for a kiss.
<p>　● Kiss in the evening. Kissing as the sun is setting or after it has fallen is more romantic than kissing during the day. You'll also feel less shy about your first kiss if you're kissing in the dark.</p>
<p>　● Kiss somewhere private. Pick a private location that is free of distractions or onlookers so you can really focus on your kiss. Pick a secluded park bench, a nice spot near a beach or a lake, or even your own balcony.</p>
<p>　● Look nice. Dress up a little bit to signify that you're about to have a special moment. You don't want to have your first kiss in your gym clothes.</p>

<img src='training_zbjw_03'/><br/>
<big>3　</big>Make sure your partner is ready. This is an important point. You can set the mood and prepare your breath all you want, but nothing you do will matter if your partner is not ready for the kiss. Before you share the kiss, make sure your partner has exhibited signs of liking you, whether it's through going on a date, touching you, or even telling you how he or she feels.
<p>　● If your partner keeps gazing into your eyes, touching you lightly, and smiling, then you'll know that she's ready for the kiss.</p>

<img src='training_zbjw_04'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>Remember to avoid some kissing pitfalls. Before you get ready for the kiss, you need to make sure to take it slow and to be gentle. If you're too aggressive or rough, your partner will get the wrong message, and the kiss will feel too forced. Here are some things to avoid before you go in for your first kiss:
<p>　● French kissing. Don't immediately shove your tongue in your partner's mouth and leave saliva everywhere. If your partner is bold and is gently touching her tongue with yours, then you can move in for a French kiss, but don't try this in the first few seconds of your traditional kiss.</p>
<p>　● Biting. Nibbling on your partner's lip or even tongue can be a kinky way to spice up your kisses. But if you do this during your first kiss, your partner will be caught off guard and may even jump back.</p>
<p>　● The roaming hands. You should make physical contact with your partner, move your bodies closer, and caress your partner's head or shoulders with your hands. You should not grope your partner in any inappropriate places during your first kiss. This is doing way too much at once, and will come off as sleazy and will make your first kiss feel insincere.</p>
            ]]></text>
    </article>
    
	
	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Improve-Your-Kissing -->
        <title>Avoiding Bad Breath</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<img src='training_kqqx_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Stay hydrated. A dry mouth can lead to bad breath and sticky lips. Make sure to drink enough fluids daily to ensure that your lips are smooth and your breath is kissable.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_kqqx_02'/><br/>
<big>2　</big>Avoid trigger foods and drinks that cause especially bad breath. More importantly, don't take your partner on a date to a restaurant that serves bad breath-inducing foods. Some common trigger foods are:
<p>
　● Garlic.<br/>
　● Onions.<br/>
　● Tuna or sardines.<br/>
　● Spicy foods.<br/>
　● Coffee.<br/>
　● Alcohol.<br/>
</p>

<img src='training_kqqx_03'/><br/>
<big>3　</big>Brush and floss your teeth twice daily. While this tip may be a given for most, there are some people who neglect to accept the basic premises of good hygiene. Make sure to brush and floss twice daily to remove any bacteria build up in your mouth. Bacteria causes bad breath. Rinse with mouthwash for an added boost of freshness.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_kqqx_04'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>Have a mint or chew some gum. Especially after consuming any food, make sure to pop a mint or chew some gum before kissing someone. If you choose to chew gum, make sure to spit it out before you start kissing. Your partner doesn't want to eat your leftover gum, and gum can also cause you to choke while kissing.<br/><br/>
            ]]></text>
    </article>
    
	
	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Improve-Your-Kissing -->
	    <title>Prepping Your Peckers</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<img src='training_zbzc_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Apply lip balm several times per day. Lip balms, especially products containing shea butter or various hydrating oils, are great for treating dry lips. Even if you generally don't have an issue with dry lips, lip balm can still make your lips even more kissable.
<p>　● Though they may taste good, avoid lip balms with artificial scents, flavors, and/or colors. These additives can actually be drying to your lips.</p>
<p>　● Common natural lip balm brands include: Burt's Bees, Carmex, Chapstick, C.O. Bigelow, Nivea, Softlips, EOS, and Banana Boat.</p>
<p>　● Right before you kiss your partner, apply a menthol-based lip balm. Menthol activates your body's cold receptors, and when you make contact with your partner, you and your partner will feel tingling sensations throughout your bodies.</p>
<p>　● Wear lip balm with at least SPF 15 when outdoors in order to protect your lips from harmful UV rays.</p>

<img src='training_zbzc_02'/><br/>
<big>2　</big>Wear an exfoliating scrub once per week. You can make an exfoliating scrub for your lips using a sugar or brown sugar base and a liquid addition. Olive oil, coconut oil, and honey all work well as additions to a sugar scrub.
<p>　● You can apply a generous coating to your lips and rub it in small circles using a toothbrush for extra exfoliation.</p>
<p>　● Be sure not to scrub too hard, you just want to remove the dead skin, not make your skin raw.</p>

<img src='training_zbzc_03'/><br/>
<big>3　</big>Eat a diet rich in fruits, vegetables, and nuts. Vitamins B, C, and Omega-3 fatty acids are extremely healthy for your skin. Make sure you are getting enough of these essential vitamins to keep your lips plump and soft.<br/><br/>
            ]]></text>
    </article>
	
	
	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Kiss -->
        <title>Kissing Techniques</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<img src='training_jw_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Keep your lips soft. Tense puckers are for family members or people you're obligated to kiss, but keeping your mouth slightly parted and soft communicates a sense of openness.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_jw_02'/><br/>
<big>2　</big>Do a few soft kisses. Start slow with soft, gentle kisses and skip the tongue and the teeth — for now. If your partner seems receptive, you can move forward to French kissing.
<p>　● Try to avoid letting your lips smack. The noise can be distracting, and might break your immersion in the moment. If you do find yourself smacking, slow down and part your lips a bit more.</p>
<p>　● Stay light at first. Avoid smashing your lips against your date's mouth — for now. Kissing softly and gently gives the other person the chance to stop if it's uncomfortable, as well as allowing you to gauge his or her interest.</p>

<p><big>3　</big>Stay at a manageable level of saliva. Slobbery puppies are the last thing you want your date thinking of while you kiss him or her. Avoid this fate by swallowing excess saliva occasionally. If you notice that your lips are a bit too wet, pull away and discreetly purse them to bring the extra spit back into your mouth.</p>

<img src='training_jw_04'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>"Lock" lips. If your initial kisses have gone well, try a lip lock, which can lead to closer kisses (and is a nice gateway for French kissing). Basically, you'll "stack" your lips so that (for instance) it looks like this:
<p>
　● Your lower lip<br/>
　● Your partner's lower lip<br/>
　● Your upper lip<br/>
　● Your partner's upper lip<br/>
　● At first, putting your date's lower lip between yours is the safest bet. Most people have larger lower lips, making them easier to grab gently with your lips.
</p>

<big>5　</big>Make sure to breathe. Ideally, you'll be able to breathe softly through your nose while you're kissing. If that's not possible, though, break away for a second to take a breath.
<p>　● Don't feel self-conscious about being out of breath or needing to take a break for a second. Breathing hard is an indication that you're nervous and excited, which your partner will probably find flattering.</p>

<img src='training_jw_06'/><br/>
<big>6　</big>Use your hands. Don't just let your hands hang at your sides like two limp fettucini noodles — put them to good use!
<p>　● Place your hands lightly on your partner's shoulders or around his or her waist. (In Western culture, girls generally put their hands on a boys shoulders while he puts his hands around her waist.)</p>
<p>　● Take the intimacy up a notch by pulling your partner in closer.</p>
<p>　● Put your hands on the sides of his or her face, using your thumb to sweep across the cheekbone, or put one hand under his or her chin and tilt it upward.</p>
<p>　● Another seriously sensual move is to put both hands around the back of your partner's head and tangle them in his or her hair, gently pulling.</p>

<img src='training_jw_07'/><br/>
<big>7　</big>Test using tongue. Once you're in a lip lock with your partner's lower lip between both of yours, lightly run the tip of your tongue over it. If you can move it slowly, even better.
<p>　● See how your partner responds. If he or she presses in closer or returns the gesture, you're probably clear to keep increasing the intensity of the kiss. If your date pulls away, maybe it's best to pull back the tongue for now and stick to lips-only kisses.</p>

<big>8　</big>Try French kissing (optional). Using your tongue during a kiss is, in Western culture, referred to as a French kiss. Why do the French get the credit? Who knows! Here's how to get started:
<p>　● Sweep your tongue along the inside of your partner's lower lip. Try to move slowly and lightly at first, increasing speed and pressure only if your partner seems to respond well.</p>
<p>　● Slide the tip of your tongue inside your partner's mouth and gently move it against the tip of his or her tongue. Use light, darting motions and keep your tongue moving — letting it sit limply in your partner's mouth isn't appealing and will bring a quick end to the kissing.</p>
<p>　● Try deeper and harder strokes if your partner seems responsive.</p>

<big>9　</big>Mix it up. Don't feel obligated to keep the intensive tongue activity going forever. Alternate soft and hard, slow and fast, deep and shallow. You can even go back to using only your lips for a few minutes.
<p>　● Alternating your technique will keep your partner from being able to predict what's coming next. Maintaining this sense of surprise and spontaneity helps your kisses avoid becoming stale.</p>

<big>10　</big>Gently nibble your partner's lips (optional). Teeth aren't a necessary element of kissing, but a grazing them over your partner's lip can introduce another unexpected element. Here are some quick pointers:
<p>　● Keep the pressure as light as possible. Remember that you're aiming to nibble, not bite.</p>
<p>　● Move slowly. Again, keeping your pace gentle will help prevent accidentally chomping on your partner's lip.</p>
<p>　● When your lips are locked, place your teeth over your partner's lower lip and slowly pull back until your teeth are almost at the end of the lip. Pause for a moment, then resume kissing as usual.</p>
<p>　● Don't break out the biters too much. They should be an occasional perk, not the main attraction.</p>
<p>　● Be prepared for rejection. Not everyone likes a side of teeth with their kisses. If your partner doesn't respond well, try not to be too offended — it's probably a matter of personal taste, not a lapse in your technique.</p>

<img src='training_jw_11'/><br/>
<big>11　</big>Increase the intensity with occasional breaks. Pull away for a moment to look into your partner's eyes, whisper something in his or her ear, or simply catch your breath and marvel at your good fortune.
<p>　● Instead of putting a damper on the action, these small moments can actually make kissing more intimate. It gives your partner the sense that you see him or her as a complete person, and not simply something to kiss.</p>
            ]]></text>
    </article>
	
	
	<article>
        <title>Setting Up the Kiss</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<p>Whether it’s a friendly kiss on the cheek or a full-on make-out session, kissing is one of life’s greatest natural pleasures. While a good kiss can increase the feelings of intimacy and love you have for your partner, a bad kiss can potentially be a deal breaker in matters of romance. Don’t panic though — even the most inexperienced people have the potential to become masters of the art of lip locking. Read this article to learn how.</p>
            
<img src='training_zjwgs_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Prepare your lips. Keep your lips relaxed and open slightly to let your partner know that you are ready for a kiss.
<p>　● Avoid puckering or pursing them, as this will send the wrong message and make kissing physically difficult.</p>
<p>　● Tackle dryness with chapstick or by licking your lips slightly. Ladies, try using lip gloss or flavored chapstick (but nothing too sticky) to make your lips irresistibly soft, shiny and tasty.</p>

<big>2　</big>Freshen your breath. The importance of good oral hygiene cannot be underestimated when it comes to kissing -- bad breath is the worst kind of turn-off.
<p>　● To avoid this, remember to floss and brush your teeth before your date and keep a small packet of mints on your person throughout the evening, so you can quickly pop one in your mouth as soon as things start to heat up.</p>
<p>　● If you're going on a dinner date, try to steer clear of very pungent or malodorous foods -- avoid things like cheese, fish, raw onions, or anything heavy on garlic.</p>
<p>　● Don't overdo it on the minty freshness though -- you don't your mouth to taste like you just swallowed an entire tube of toothpaste!</p>

<img src='training_zjwgs_02'/><br/>
<big>3　</big>Set the mood. Let your partner know that you want to kiss him or her by maintaining eye contact and smiling.
<p>　● If you are in the middle of a conversation, then slow it down and lower your voice slightly to signal that you’re ready to stop talking and start smooching.</p>
<p>　● Some people get so nervous before the first kiss with a new partner that they end up talking too much in order to fill the silence. Avoid doing this as it could ruin the moment and make your partner lose interest.</p>

<img src='training_zjwgs_03'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>Lean in for a kiss. When you're ready and you think the moment is right, take a step closer to your partner and lean in for the kiss.<br/><br/>
<p>　● If you want to add to the romance, you can do something intimate like touching your partner's face or brushing the hair out of their eyes right before you lean in.</p>
<p>　● Watch your partner as you lean in to determine whether to tilt your head to the left or to the right. Remember to move your head in the opposite direction to your partner’s.</p>
<p>　● You should also tilt your head back slightly and point your lips and chin forward to avoid banging your foreheads together.</p>

<big>5　</big>Close your eyes. Sometimes in the nervousness leading up to a first kiss, you can forget to close your eyes. This is bad for two reasons:<br/><br/>
<p>　● Firstly, it probably means that you are overthinking things. Closing your eyes allows you to relax, let go of your inhibitions and just enjoy the moment.</p>
<p>　● Secondly, if your partner opens their eyes during the kiss and finds you staring straight back at them, it would be kind of creepy and probably kill the romance.</p>
<p>　● A word of warning though -- don't close your eyes until after you have found the other person's lips, otherwise you're likely to bump foreheads.</p>

<img src='training_zjwgs_04'/><br/>
<big>6　</big>Start off slow. Keep your lips ever so slightly open, but avoid using your tongue at first. Start off with a few slow, gentle kisses, lingering on your partner’s lips each time.
<p>　● Keep things interesting by repositioning your lips in between each kiss. Tilt your head slightly more to the left or slightly more to the right, or switch sides entirely so that your head is now tilted in the opposite direction as before.</p>

<img src='training_zjwgs_05'/><br/>
<big>7　</big>Open your mouth a little more. Once you have been kissing without tongue for a bit, it’s time to take it to the next level. Lock lips with your partner so that his or her bottom lip is in between your two lips, and then open your mouth slightly to signify that you’re ready to French kiss.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_zjwgs_06'/><br/>
<big>8　</big>Use your tongue. Start off gently at first, moving your tongue into the front of your partner’s mouth. Avoid immediately jamming your tongue too far into his or her mouth, as this can be a major turn-off. Move your tongue in slow, fluid movements around the other person’s tongue and allow them to reciprocate before going any further.
<p>　● Start off by gently touching the tip of your tongue to the tip of your partner’s tongue. If both of you feel comfortable with it, you can move your tongue deeper into your partner’s mouth and begin massaging their tongue with yours.</p>
<p>　● Pay attention to your partner’s movements. Being a good kisser is about being in sync with the other person and finding a rhythm that works for both of you.</p>

<img src='training_zjwgs_07'/><br/>
<big>9　</big>Use your hands. Place your hands gently on your partner’s waist, shoulders, face, or neck. If things get heated up, grab your partner harder and move your hands from one body part to the other.
<p>　● Increase the intensity of the moment by placing your hands on the back of your partner’s head and grabbing his or her hair.</p>

<big>10　</big>Do something different. Being a good kisser isn't about doing everything perfectly -- that can become a little mechanical. Sometimes it's good to throw something a bit different into the mix, something that surprises your partner (in a good way) and leaves them wanting more.<br/>
<p>　● Try licking the center of your partner's open lips with your tongue, or using your tongue to briefly stroke the roof of their mouth. They may find this unusual, but super sexy.</p>
<p>　● Try inhaling through your mouth instead of your nose when your lips are sealed together -- like you're taking their breath into your body. This can be extremely intimate -- as long as it's not overused.</p>
<p>　● Try gently (we said gently) biting or sucking your partner's lower or upper lip. If done correctly, this can be a major turn-on for the other person.</p>
<p>　● Try moving away from your partner's lips and spend a little time kissing their neck instead -- women are particularly fond of this move.</p>

<img src='training_zjwgs_08'/><br/>
<big>11　</big>Don’t forget to breathe. Since your mouth is occupied, you will need to breathe through your nose while kissing. If you are not getting enough air that way, then pull your face away from your partner’s every once in awhile to catch your breath.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_zjwgs_09'/><br/>
<big>12　</big>Be passionate. The more excited you are about the kiss, the more excited your partner will be. You should be completely present in the moment and try to avoid letting your mind wander to other things. Allow yourself to relax, and don’t spend the entire time wondering what the other person is thinking — go with the flow and have fun!<br/><br/>

<img src='training_zjwgs_10'/><br/>
<big>13　</big>Decide when and where to kiss this person. Non-romantic kisses are appropriate for friends and family members who you care for deeply. These types of kisses are appropriate for the cheek, hand and forehead in some instances.
<p>　● In many cultures, it is appropriate to kiss a friend or family member once or twice on the cheek when greeting each other or parting ways. Forehead kisses are usually more romantic in nature, and are appropriate for lovers, close friends, and/or exes.</p>

<img src='training_zjwgs_11'/><br/>
<big>14　</big>Pucker your lips. For a friendly kiss, you should always keep your lips pursed together and completely dry. Wet kisses can be extremely unpleasant, so be sure to wipe your mouth beforehand if necessary!
<p>　● Ladies, if you are wearing lipstick or lipgloss, it might be a good idea to wipe it off with a napkin beforehand (unless, of course, you are purposely trying to leave a kiss-mark on this person’s cheek!)</p>

<img src='training_zjwgs_12'/><br/>
<big>15　</big>Go in for the kiss. Be sure to keep the kiss(es) short and sweet to avoid sending the wrong message or making the other person feel uncomfortable. Avoid lingering too long, unless you are hoping that the non-romantic kiss will turn into something more than that.<br/>

<p>
<h1>Tips</h1>
　☞ Relax. Kissing should be an enjoyable activity. The more relaxed and confident you feel, the better your kisses will be.<br/>
　☞ The best way to keep your lips kissably soft year-round is to stay properly hydrated and exfoliate your lips occasionally using a toothbrush or loofah.<br/>
　☞ As with any other skill, French kissing takes practice. The more experience you have, the less nervous you will feel and the more you will learn about how to please your partner(s).<br/>
　☞ Be fully present. If you are bored, distracted, or overly nervous, it will be hard to deliver a passionate kiss. If you are excited, your partner will be, too.<br/>
　☞ Make sure both you and your partner are comfortable.<br/>
　☞ Mints are your best friends. Pop one in about 10 minutes before the end of the date. Avoid chewing gum as your partner doesn't want to feel that in your mouth.<br/>
</p>
            ]]></text>
    </article>

	
	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/French-Kiss -->
        <title>French Kiss</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<p>You've seen it done in the movies and probably even in public — the French kiss, a timeless and passionate gesture of romantic affection. Whether you live in Paris, France or Paris, Texas, you can learn how to kiss like the French do without an embarrassing faux pas!</p>

<img src='training_fssw_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Keep your lips soft. A soft, smooth and slightly-moist mouth is ideal for kissing. Before you move in, try to make sure your lips aren't chapped and dry with these quick fixes:
<p>　● Use chapstick. Swipe some over your lips and press them together. (If you're a girl and you have flavored chapstick, all the better!)</p>
<p>　● Drink water. Dry lips are a sign of dehydration, so throw back a tall glass of water (or two). You should notice your lips starting to smooth out within 20 to 30 minutes.</p>
<p>　● Lick your lips. If you're really in a pinch and have no time to spare, quickly run your tongue over your lips and press them together. This should moisten them slightly without making them slobbery or slick.</p>

<big>2　</big>Freshen your breath. You never want to have bad breath when you are about to kiss someone, whether the kiss is a French kiss or not. Because your mouth will be open in a French kiss, fresh breath is especially important. Practice good dental hygiene. If you know you are about to kiss someone, take a second to brush your teeth or at least rinse out your mouth with water.
<p>　● Always have breath mints or mint-flavored gum with you if you think there is a chance you might kiss someone while you are out.</p>
<p>　● Avoid foods that leave an unpleasant aftertaste or residue, particularly garlic, coffee, onions, milk, and corn.</p>

<big>3　</big>Find the right moment. A good kiss—especially a first kiss or first French kiss—is the culmination of a building tension and growing intimacy. Choose your moment right to make sure you and your partner are both in a mindset to really lose yourselves in the kiss. When is the moment right? It depends on your individual situation, but here are a few signs to keep in mind:
<p>　● The other person keeps dropping hints, like locking eyes and looking at your lips, or standing or sitting progressively closer to you. Whether you are kissing a boy or a girl, their body language should give you a clue about whether now is the right time to make your move.</p>
<p>　● You're ending a date that went really well. In the car or on the porch are both good semi-private locations for a goodnight kiss.</p>
<p>　● It just seems right. If you overwhelmingly compelled to kiss someone, don't be too afraid to just go for it. (Just be prepared for an awkward or even troubling situation if you discover your victim didn't feel the same way.)</p>
<p>　● Ask. If you aren't sure whether the other person is feeling it, bring up the topic. Better to get permission semi-awkwardly and go ahead with confidence than risk missing out on your chance to kiss that special someone (accidentally kiss someone who isn't interested).</p>

<p><big>4　</big>Make eye contact. Gaze deeply into the other person's eyes. If you want to make your intentions extra clear, slowly move your gaze to his or her lips, then back up to the eyes.</p>
<p><big>5　</big>Smile. If you're really excited about the prospect of kissing the other person, show it! A smile keeps the situation light and fun, while helping him or her feel safe and relaxed. Make sure your smile is soft and genuine, however, and not a forced, too-wide, or creepy smile.</p>

<big>6　</big>Move in. When the moment seems right, go in for the approach! In general, you should be moving slowly enough that the other person has time to say no, but not so slow that the moment loses its spark.
<p>　● Take it slow. The slow approach builds tension and anticipation. Move in at a pace that gives the other person a chance to consent (or not). When they see you coming in, they may move to meet you, so going slow will prevent you from accidentally bumping heads.</p>

<img src='training_fssw_02'/><br/>
<big>7　</big>Tilt your head slightly to one side. Meeting head-on will result in bumping noses. Instead, just tilt your head slightly to the left or right. If you notice the other person going in one direction, pick the opposite.

<p><big>8　</big>Close your eyes. Just before you make contact, close your eyes. Kissing with your eyes open is generally associated with dishonesty and insincerity, and keeping your eyes closed will help you focus on and enjoy what's happening on your lips.</p>

<img src='training_fssw_03'/><br/>
<big>9　</big>Keep your mouth in a kissable position. Don't present a stiff pucker, like you would if you went in to kiss your grandma — not only does it communicate non-romantic feelings, it makes it physically difficult for your partner to initiate a French kiss. On the other hand, keeping your mouth completely loose and still also says that you're not interested. Here's how to hit a happy medium:
<p>　● Pucker just a little. Push your lips forward slightly, so that you feel the slightest hint of muscle tension around them.</p>
<p>　● Open your mouth slightly. Instead of aggressively going in for a fully open-mouthed kiss at first, keep your lips just barely parted enough that a tongue could slip between them.</p>

<img src='training_fssw_04'/><br/>
<big>10　</big>Lightly brush your lips over the other person's. Use feather-light pressure at first, so that your lips are just barely grazing over your partner's. This builds more anticipation and excitement than diving straight into a full-on French kiss.
<p>　● Keep your movements slow. A lot of quick, light kisses don't have the same level of sexiness as a barely-restrained build in tension. Act like you have all the time in the world—the kiss will speed up soon enough.</p>

<img src='training_fssw_05'/><br/>
<big>11　</big>Test the waters. Once you've built a solid foundation for a French kiss with some tongueless kissing, you can give the other person some subtle hints that you're ready to take it up a notch.
<p>　● Open your mouth more widely. Offering unrestricted access invites the other person to make the first tentative tongue contact.</p>
<p>　● Lock lips, so that the other person's lower lip is between your two lips. Then, lightly sweep the tip of your tongue over the lower lip. Do one smooth, swift motion so that the contact lasts for less than a second. If he or she is interested, they'll reciprocate.</p>
<p>　● Know when to pull back. If you've tried both of the above techniques and your partner hasn't responded, simply leave it alone until next time and focus on regular kissing. Avoid making a big deal of it, or guilting him or her.</p>

<img src='training_fssw_06'/><br/>
<big>12　</big>Explore with your tongue. If the other person seems interested, go ahead and start French kissing for real. Remember to keep your tongue in motion and your touches light.
<p>　● Stay playful. "Tag" the other person's tongue lightly and retreat back, inviting him or her to make the next move.</p>
<p>　● Tongues are loaded with nerve endings, and the mere act of touching your partner's tongue with your own will be very pleasant.</p>
<p>　● Don't go too deep — jamming your tongue down the other person's throat is a big turn-off. Stay shallow and light at first.</p>

<img src='training_fssw_07'/><br/>
<big>13　</big>Breathe. If you’re kissing for an extended period, it’s easy to forget to breathe. Believe it or not, gasping and turning blue isn't very romantic. Here's how to keep up:
<p>　● Take small breaths through your nose as you kiss.</p>
<p>　● Don't be afraid to take a break. If you do it right, it can still be an intimate and sexy moment. Pull back slightly so that your foreheads are still touching, make eye contact, and smile.</p>
<p>　● As you and your partner grow comfortable with the kiss, you can try breathing through your mouth a little: sharing breaths as well can be romantic (but not everybody likes it).</p>

<img src='training_fssw_08'/><br/>
<big>14　</big>Mix it up. Kisses are like snowflakes: no two are exactly the same. Once you feel comfortable French kissing someone, it is tempting to try to do the same thing every time, but resist. Add variety! Here's what you can vary:
<p>　● Speed: Varying the speed of your kisses is a good way to try something different without potentially intimidating your partner. Once you've got the slow kiss mastered, try going a little faster for a few seconds — it should leave you both a little breathless!</p>
<p>　● Depth: Once you're comfortable with someone, try kissing a little more deeply. The key to pulling this off is keeping your speed under control. Or, if you want things to be a little more flirty and playful, return to shallow kisses.</p>
<p>　● Pressure: Like a deep kiss, a hard kiss should be reserved for a situation in which you already know both you and your partner are comfortable. Be a little bit more forceful with your tongue, but be sure to keep it in motion.</p>
<p>　● Teeth: You may want to try rubbing the backs or front of the other person's teeth with your tongue. This can create a ticklish feeling that might enhance your kiss. You could also try lightly catching the other person's lower lip with your teeth. Be aware, though, that not everyone likes their kisses with a side of teeth — be prepared to put your chompers away.</p>

<img src='training_fssw_09'/><br/>
<big>15　</big>Use your hands. While you should keep your hands polite, especially on a first kiss, you don’t necessarily want them just dangling at your sides.
<p>　● As a general rule, start with your hands on your partner's hips and then slowly move them around their back or up to the face and hair.</p>
<p>　● Another turn-on for the first kiss is to gently caress the other person's shoulder. It shows you are comfortable with him or her.</p>
<p>　● Cradle your partner's face with your hands on their cheeks and their neck.</p>
<p>　● Or, go for an old standby: simply wrap your arms around your partner in an embrace.</p>

<img src='training_fssw_10'/><br/>
<big>16　</big>Read your partner's body language. Everybody kisses a little differently, and each person enjoys different things in a kiss — there is no "right" way to kiss. Good kissing requires give-and-take, so read your partner’s body language and pay attention to clues that tell you you’re doing something he or she likes.
<p>　● Not everybody likes to be kissed the same way, so while your former partner might have enjoyed one method of kissing, your new love might not. You need to learn to read signals and adapt to a style that's comfortable for each of you.</p>
<p>　● If your partner pulls away or seems uncomfortable at any time, understand that you have to slow it down.</p>
<p>　● Let your partner kiss you back, and move with him or her as long as you’re comfortable with what he or she is doing.</p>
<p>　● Listen for clues that tell how much your partner is enjoying a particular maneuver. If you hear a sigh or moan, or they begin kissing you back with increased intensity, you're on the right track.</p>

<img src='training_fssw_11'/><br/>
<big>17　</big>Practice. Good French kissing, like good kissing of any kind, requires practice. You will get better as you do it more. In addition, the more practice you have with one person, the more comfortable you will feel kissing them and developing a style that suits both of you.<br/><br/>

<big>18　</big>Communicate. If you really like the way your partner kisses you, let them know. If you don't like something, also let your partner know that, but approach it delicately and compliment them at the same time on something they did that you liked.
<p>　● Even if the kiss goes all wrong, it can still be an intimate affair if you can both laugh about it together! Make sure when you kiss you are having fun doing what you are doing.</p>

<p>
<h1>Tips</h1>
　☞ There are no rules for how long you should hold a kiss. If you feel uncomfortable at any time, break the kiss; otherwise, just enjoy it until one or both of you slowly pull apart, usually together. Some find it extremely romantic if you lightly suck your partner's upper or bottom lip as you part. You might find yourselves returning to kissing, after each of you takes a breath.<br/>
　☞ Be an active partner. If someone is French kissing you and you want them to do so, do not just sit there but get into the kiss. Reciprocate their actions, and alternate taking the lead on the movements of your tongues and lips. If you are uncomfortable with any part of the kiss, do not be afraid to pull away or gently close your lips. This will give your partner the hint.<br/>
　☞ Excessive saliva can build up during a French kiss, and that can interfere with the romantic moment. Swallow periodically without breaking the kiss. If you have trouble doing that, do not be afraid to pull away for a moment. Smiling when you pull away can reassure your partner that you're just taking a small break, not rejecting their affection.<br/>
　☞ If you ever feel uncomfortable or do not want to move forward with any move your partner is attempting, pull away and let your partner know that you want to stop. Be firm. It's okay to say no.<br/>
　☞ Be aware that French kissing may transmit infectious diseases such as herpes and infectious mononucleosis (also known as mono).<br/>
　☞ You can still French kiss if one or both of you has braces, but you should be careful to prevent the braces from touching each other. Also avoid touching the braces with your tongue (you might accidentally cut yourself). Check out How to Kiss with Braces.<br/>
</p>
            ]]></text>
    </article>
    
	
	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Kiss-in-a-Variety-of-Ways -->
        <title>Kiss in a Variety of Ways</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<p>Are you bored with regular kissing and french kissing, or do you just want to spice up your love life? Whether you're an experienced kisser or you're still learning the ropes, you can learn to kiss in so many different ways that you and your partner won't want to stop! Follow these easy steps to learn to kiss in a variety of fun and sexy ways.</p>

<big>1　</big>The trade-off kiss. This is a fun and advanced kiss that you should try with someone you are comfortable kissing. During this kiss, on person should suck on a cinnamon candy and the other should suck on a mint. Begin to French kiss. Slowly switch the mints and the candy in your mouths.
<p>　● Switch the mint and the candy back and forth until you need to come up for air or until they have dissolved.</p>
<p>　● You can do the trade-off kiss with any small candies or mints, but be careful not to choke on them.</p>
<p>　● If you're nervous, start the kiss by practicing trading just one item between your mouths to get the hang of it.</p>

<big>2　</big>The flavor kiss. First, put a piece of long-lasting gum in your mouth just before you and your partner French kiss. While you're kissing, pass the gum back and forth, and see how long it takes for the flavor to run out!
<p>　● Choose a gum with a sexy flavor, like strawberry or winter mint.</p>

<big>3　</big>The drink kiss. Take a sip of your favorite drink, which could be either something alcoholic or sweet. Begin to kiss your partner, and when your lips meet, pour the drink into your partner's mouth. Take a very small sip of the drink to avoid spilling it.
<p>　● Your first attempt should be with a clear substance so you don't end up spilling it everywhere.</p>

<img src='training_ydzfsjw_04'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>The cold kiss. Take a few sips of an ice-cold drink or chew on an ice cube until your mouth is freezing. Then, kiss your partner and graze your tongues. You will feel a sexy chill if you do it right.<br/><br/>

<big>5　</big>The Pop Rocks kiss. Pour a little bit of Pop Rocks into your partner's mouth and then begin to French kiss him.
<p>　● Both of you will feel a playful tingle in your mouths.</p>

<big>6　</big>The breath kiss. This kiss creates major anticipation in an already-hot moment. First, you and your partner should part your lips slightly, and barely touch them. Begin to share your partner's breath. You can move your heads to experience different sensations, and touch your lips on and off slightly. This is a teasing kiss that will leave both of you wanting more and will make you feel very sexy.
<p>　● Remember that hot breath is different from cool breath. Breathing from your throat will create hot breath, while blowing through your lips will create cool air.</p>
<p>　● Obviously, both partners should have fresh breath before they jump into this kiss.</p>

<img src='training_ydzfsjw_07'/><br/>
<big>7　</big>The underwater kiss. This can be tricky, but rewarding. First, your partner should hold his breath underwater. Next, he should pull you down. You should join him with lungs full of air. Gently begin to kiss him, and share your air with him.
<p>　● When you get this method down, switch and be the person who is underwater first.</p>
<p>　● Be careful with this one. You could end up choking on water. Start your kiss by parting your lips just a tiny bit.</p>

<big>8　</big>The vacuum kiss. This is a playful kiss. Kiss your partner with an open mouth, and suck in so deeply that you're sucking away your partner's air.
<p>　● Fresh breath is also a must for this one.</p>

<big>9　</big>The chew kiss. This kiss is not for the faint of heart. First, your partner should put his tongue deeply in your mouth. Then you should gently bite the back of his tongue. For added effect, you could suck the tip of his tongue as well.
<p>　● Take turns. After you've worked your way around your partner's tongue, put your tongue into his mouth and enjoy the kiss.</p>

<big>10　</big>The touch kiss. This is a kiss for experienced French kissers. During this kiss, you and your partner should simply touch the tips of your tongues. Your tongues should be touching outside your mouths. Move your tongues around for more pleasure.
<p>　● The touch kiss can feel great, but avoid offending the people around you. Kissing in public is one thing, but kissing with your tongues in the open takes it to a new level.</p>

<big>11　</big>The suck kiss. This is a seductive type of kiss. Instead of a normal French kiss, suck on your partner's top or bottom lip while he is kissing you. You can suck for just one or two seconds and then switch between the bottom and top lip.
<p>　● Switch and have your partner suck on your lips.</p>
<p>　● Don't try to suck on each other's lips at the same time. That will be too messy.</p>

<p><big>12　</big>The chin kiss. Hold your partner's chin with your middle finger, index finger, and thumb. Tilt his head in the right direction. Continue to hold it as you kiss. Note that you can chin kiss any way you want. As long as you're supporting his chin, you can French kiss or add other elements to the kiss that involve your tongue and lips.</p>

<big>13　</big>The nip kiss. This kiss needs to be carefully done, but if you do it right, your partner will feel amazing. First, bite your partner's lip very gently. Then be slightly more aggressive and try biting other parts of your partner's lips.
<p>　● You should only try this one with someone you've kissed a lot, because not everyone is comfortable with biting.</p>

<big>14　</big>The foot kiss. The foot kiss is both an erotic and a romantic gesture. Before you begin, make sure you have your partner's consent, because some people are weird about their feet. Next, make sure your partner's feet are clean and ready to be kissed. Begin by gently sucking the toes and then lightly kissing the foot.
<p>　● While you kiss your partner's foot, give her a gentle foot massage at the same time.</p>
<p>　● Lightly blow on your partner's toes.</p>
<p>　● Don't kiss your partner's feet if he wore sneakers or close-toed shoes all day because his feet could be sweaty and damp. The best time to do this is after he is freshly showered.</p>
<p>　● If you know that your partner plans on kissing your feet, keep your toenails neatly trimmed and manicured.</p>

<p><big>15　</big>The forehead kiss. This is not an erotic kiss, but is meant to show your affection, or even to say goodnight to your loved one. Simply brush your lips lightly on the crown of your loved one's head. You can even push your loved one's hair back for effect.</p>
<p><big>16　</big>The Eskimo kiss. This one is simple. Rub noses with your partner and don't forget to smile.</p>
<p><big>17　</big>The cheek kiss. This is a great way to greet your partner or to say goodbye. Just gently kiss your partner on his cheek.</p>
<p><big>18　</big>The butterfly kiss. Move your face close to your partner's until your eyelashes are touching. Then, bat your eyelashes at the same time.</p>

<p>
<h1>Tips</h1>
　☞ Surprise your partner with an upside-down kiss. While your partner is sitting down, stand behind him or her, and tip his or her head back gently. Then lean down to begin kissing upside down. Be careful to avoid hitting your teeth, but once you get the hang of it, you can be more aggressive and even French kiss.<br/>
　☞ Try these kisses after you've mastered regular kissing and French kissing with your partner. Otherwise you may not be ready for something so adventurous.<br/>
　☞ If you have braces, it is imperative that you keep them clean!<br/>
　☞ Give them a ride in your car and make jokes and make them laugh, and by the time she sees you just hold her hands and kiss!<br/>
　☞ Be sure not to choke on any of the types of kisses that involve mints or gum.<br/>
</p>
            ]]></text>
    </article>
	
	
	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Improve-Your-Kissing -->
        <title>Using Your Whole Body</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<img src='training_xhystgjwjq_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Pay attention to your partner's body language. Kissing isn't just about paying attention to what you and your partner's lips are doing. Your whole body should be involved in the act of making out to achieve the most sensual and pleasurable experience possible. The way your partner moves the rest of his/her body while you are kissing can tell you a lot about how they are feeling and what they think about your performance.
<p>　● Positive signs to look for: Your partner pulling you closer, squeezing you with his/her hands, kissing and caressing with a sense of intense urgency, breaking into random smiles or giggles, or frequent sighing. If you notice that your partner reacts in a particularly positive way to certain actions, be sure to take note. Your partner will appreciate your attentiveness and definitely recognize that you are making an impressive effort to understand what makes them feel the best.</p>
<p>　● Negative signs to look for: Your partner pulling away, pushing your shoulder away, not touching you at all with his/her hands, barely moving his/her lips, or trying to close his/her lips as much as possible to force you to stop.</p>

<img src='training_xhystgjwjq_02'/><br/>
<big>2　</big>Caress your partner's neck, ears, and face. A mini massage of these sensitive areas can be extremely arousing. Lightly run your fingers and gently run your thumb in a sweeping motion over these areas.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_xhystgjwjq_03'/><br/>
<big>3　</big>Grab your partner's arms, shoulders and back. You can be a little more rough with these areas. A tight squeeze of your partner can send chills throughout their body. If you're feeling particularly sassy, give your partner a little butt squeeze. You'll be able to tell where they like to be touched by their body language.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_xhystgjwjq_04'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>Place your hands on your partner's shoulders or around his/her waist. Move your fingers and/or thumb gently back and forth in a swaying motion to sweetly show your partner that you're there.
<p>　● While women generally put their hands on a man's shoulders and men generally wrap their arms around a woman's waist, your position will more practically depend on the height difference between you and your partner.</p>
<p>　● That being said, the placement isn't really important, the recognition of each other is what counts.</p>

<img src='training_xhystgjwjq_05'/><br/>
<big>5　</big>Take your index finger or thumb and use it to lift up you partner's chin as you look into his/her eyes. Then go in for the kiss. This slight moment of visual recognition coupled with a light touch can be subtly pleasant.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_xhystgjwjq_06'/><br/>
<big>6　</big>Gently pull on your partner's hair by running your fingers through the hair on the back of his/her head just above the neck. These gentle pulls really say "I want you."<br/><br/>
            ]]></text>
    </article>
		
	
	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Improve-Your-Kissing -->
        <title>Learning the Technique</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<img src='training_tgjwjq_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Take the slow approach. Lean in slowly for the kiss to build dramatic anticipation. The more excited you and your partner are for a kiss to commence, the more intense it will be when you finally connect your lips.
<p>　● Start off with small pecks and build up to bigger and more intense kissing. By starting small you can slowly ease into an intimate act with your partner.</p>
<p>　● Take breaks between kissing your partner to look at one another without touching lips. You can leave your hands on your partner's hips, shoulders, or run your hands across your partner's face in smooth caresses. By staring into your partner's eyes, you can show him/her that you are truly absorbed in them as a unique person.</p>

<img src='training_tgjwjq_02'/><br/>
<big>2　</big>Leave the slobbering to your dog. There's nothing worse than a slobbery kiss. Just nothing. Other than making you appear to have no idea what you're doing, nobody wants to have your spit all over their face. Well, maybe just a little bit of spit.
<p>　● Avoid opening your mouth too wide. A wide-mouthed approach can cause you to lose a ridiculous amount of saliva to your partner's precious face.</p>
<p>　● Swallow often. Don't forget to swallow your excess saliva while kissing. Your spit has to go somewhere, just dont make it your partner's face.</p>

<img src='training_tgjwjq_03'/><br/>
<big>3　</big>Keep your lips gently pursed. You want your lips to be in a nice plump purse, but avoid pursing your lips too tightly. If you tighten your lips together too strongly in a protruding kissy face, your lips will loose their plumpness and will not be as luscious for kissing.(Ladies: this is the same kissy face you make when putting on your lipstick!)<br/><br/>

<img src='training_tgjwjq_04'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>Tilt your head slightly to one side or the other. Most right-handed people will feel more natural tilting their head to the right, and left-handed people will prefer to tilt left. The important thing is that you and your partner are tilting the same direction (i.e. both to the right or both to the left), which will create a mirror-effect and allow you to lock lips.
<p>　● Transition smoothly between tilting your head to the right and the left. You can make your kissing game more interesting by changing up movements from side to side every few kisses. The transition should come at the end of a kiss and the beginning of another.</p>
<p>　● Don't move your head from side to side too frequently. Doing so can create sloppy rhythm and can become uncomfortable for both people involved.</p>

<img src='training_tgjwjq_05'/><br/>
<big>5　</big>Use your tongue to French kiss. Slowly and lightly sweep your tongue along your partner's lower lip, tongue, and gums. Start off very gently and slowly increase in pressure and pace as your partner starts to return the tongue action.
<p>　● Don't stick your entire tongue in your partner's mouth, you really only need to use about the front third of your tongue. Use quick, sweeping motions and make sure that your tongue is constantly moving. Letting your tongue fall limp in your partner's mouth is not sexy.</p>
<p>　● This is where it can really get slobbery. Make sure to swallow often to avoid allowing too much saliva to build up in your mouth and spill over into your partner's mouth. There is a fine line between sexy and slobbery. Try not to cross it.</p>

<img src='training_tgjwjq_06'/><br/>
<big>6　</big>Break up the kissing with romantic stares. Pull your lips apart every once in awhile to put some space between you and your partner and gaze into each other's eyes. Taking a break can make your kissing all the more intense once you reconnect. Plus, there's no better way to show someone you are truly paying attention to them than by staring sweetly into their eyes.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_tgjwjq_07'/><br/>
<big>7　</big>Be creative. Try different gentle nibbling/sucking/kissing/tongue combinations to keep it fresh and exciting.
<p>　● Give the "lip-o-suction" move a try. Kiss your partner's upper lip while your partner nibbles and sucks on your lower lip, then switch.</p>
<p>　● Interrupt your kissing with small bites and nibbles. A sensual nibble on your partner's bottom lip can break up with rhythm of lip kissing in a good way. Be careful not to bite your partner's lip too hard, you're not trying to eat your partner's face.</p>
<p>　● Mix in small pecks with larger, more passionate kisses. Doing so adds variety and allows you to take breaks in between intense make-out sessions.</p>
            ]]></text>
    </article>
    
	
	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Kiss-a-Neck -->
        <title>Kiss a Neck</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<p>Whether you're new to the technique or you just want to take your partner's breath away, wikiHow can help you improve this vital kissing skill.</p>
<img src='training_qwbz_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Work on your lips. No one wants to kiss cracked, dry lips! The silkier the lips, the easier a time you'll have kissing. A quick lick will do in a pinch, but for the best kisses you should moisturize those lips. Keep yourself hydrated, and apply products like lip balm. Products like Burt's Bees, Carmex, or Bag Balm can get your lips smooth and silky.
<p>　● A lip gloss can make your lips even juicer for kissing, if you like wearing that kind of thing.</p>

<big>2　</big>Sweeten the deal. Good breath with a sweet taste to your lips are important for any make out session. Neck kisses often result in your breath going straight to their face, so be prepared.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_qwbz_03'/><br/>
<big>3　</big>Start subtle. Don't start the make out session at the neck. Start at the mouth and make your way there. This is much sexier (although, there's certainly something to be said for those sneaky-from-behind neck kisses). Trail kisses from mouth to neck for ultimate effect.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_qwbz_04'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>Go slow. Not slow as in "I'm not sure about this" but slow as in "I know exactly what I'm doing and you're going to beg me for it". Enjoy each touch, each texture, each flavor as you move across their skin. This will have them...eager for more.<br/><br/>

<big>5　</big>Vary pressure. You should vary between the lightest of kisses and firm, strong kiss. The variation is what makes the kiss (and make outs in general) more interesting and fun. You don't want to seem robotic!<br/><br/>
<big>6　</big>Nibble. A little nibble or even a strong bite can be a huge turn-on for your partner. This is most effective on the side of the neck, rather than the front or back. Be careful though: this is an easy way to leave marks or a bruise, which may land your partner in hot water with family, school, or work.<br/><br/>
<big>7　</big>Suck. Then, of course, there's the classic sucking. This is most sensual if, like varying pressure, it is a quick suck and then release, perhaps interspersed with other techniques. Be careful though: this is an easy way to leave marks or a bruise, which may land your partner in hot water with family, school, or work.<br/><br/>
<big>9　</big>Lick. Whether a quick probe with the tongue or a long sensual lick from earlobe to collarbone, licking is an important part of a good neck kiss. This is also safer than biting or sucking, as it's not going to leave any marks!<br/><br/>

<img src='training_qwbz_10'/><br/>
<big>10　</big>Vary temperature. Changes in temperature trigger those sexy tingly nerves. Get such changes in temperature by lightly blowing over some skin you've just licked. A hot sensation can be created by nuzzling or by blowing out a big puff of air (like you're trying to see your breath). The cold is more effective than the hot, however, contrary to what you'd think.<br/><br/>

<big>11　</big>Make some sounds. Moaning, whispered dirty talk, and sometimes even a growl can be a sexy sound for your partner to hear while you nibble. Don't be afraid to make a little sound!<br/><br/>
<big>12　</big>Keep your hands moving. While you're kissing, you should be moving your hands to caress their chest, cup their face, grope their...erm...you get the idea. You don't want to seem like a dead fish. Show them just how alive you are by overloading their body with sensation.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_qwbz_13'/><br/>
<big>13　</big>Don't stay too long. Some people enjoy an hour long neck-snog, but generally neck kissing should be a prelude to something else. You especially don't want to linger too long on the neck, as hickeys can really get your partner in a lot of trouble.<br/><br/>

<big>14　</big>Keeping exploring. Apply these techniques to a variety of places on your partner's body. All of the nerve endings that make neck kisses feel so good can also be found in other places, like the inner thigh or the wrist. Bonus: hickeys in these spots are way easier to hide!<br/><br/>
<big>15　</big>Come back from time to time. Just wander back to the neck every now and again, trailing kisses like we talked about. The variety is what makes for a great make out.<br/><br/>
<big>16　</big>Get rid of the evidence. If you're really going to insist on ignoring our hickey warnings, we can at least keep you prepared on what to do when you get one!<br/>
            ]]></text>
    </article>

	<article>
	    <!-- http://www.wikihow.com/Remove-a-Hickey -->
        <title>Remove a Hickey</title>
        <text><![CDATA[
<p>Sure, you might have thought getting a hickey was a great idea in the heat of the moment, but you may have changed your mind once you heard that you have to show up to your great Aunt Martha's retirement party picnic the next day. How are you going to show up looking classy instead of embarrassing yourself in front of your family? Read on to find out.</p>

<img src='training_xcwh_01'/><br/>
<big>1　</big>Cool the hickey. Apply an icepack or cold spoon on the hickey as soon as possible after you get it. You can wrap some ice in a towel, use pre-frozen ice packs or put a spoon in the freezer for a few minutes. Gently hold the cold compress to the skin for several minutes (up to 20 minutes, if it doesn’t feel too uncomfortable), remove the compress for several minutes, and then apply it again.
<p>　● If you're using a spoon, you will need to chill the spoon in the freezer first. You must use a lot of pressure with the spoon but should see results over a few minutes of doing this.</p>

<img src='training_xcwh_02'/><br/>
<big>2　</big>Brush your hickey with a toothbrush. A new toothbrush is preferably, obviously. Many people swear by this technique for getting rid of hickeys. Here is what you'll have to do:
<p>　● Lightly brush the hickey and the area around it with a stiff-bristled toothbrush or a comb. Doing this stimulates circulation, but pressing too hard can make the hickey worse, so be gentle.</p>
<p>　● Wait about 15 minutes. The redness and swelling will spread, but will be less obvious after about 15 minutes.</p>
<p>　● Apply a cold compress, as above.</p>
<p>　● Repeat if necessary. Depending on the magnitude of your hickey, this method may work or it may just spread the discoloration a bit.</p>

<img src='training_xcwh_03'/><br/>
<big>3　</big>Scrape your skin with a coin. This method is the most painful, but it can give you real results. To do this, first, stretch the skin around the hickey flat by pulling away from the hickey on opposite sides. Then, use the edge of a large coin to scrape the skin. Use the coin like the hickey was butter on toast, and spread outward. You must press quite hard (as hard as you can, but not so that you break the skin, bleed or hurt).
<p>　● What some people believe this does is push the excess blood, which has escaped from the capillaries, out of the surface skin.</p>
<p>　● There will be redness from the scraping, but that will go away much faster than a hickey. Even then, a scrape is much less conspicuous than a hickey.</p>

<img src='training_xcwh_04'/><br/>
<big>4　</big>Apply a layer of toothpaste to the hickey. Gently rub some toothpaste onto the hickey and leave it there for a few minutes. Then, when it stops tingling, remove the toothpaste with a warm washcloth. Wait 24 hours and repeat if necessary. You'll see better results if you can do this as soon as possible.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_xcwh_05'/><br/>
<big>5　</big>Conceal the hickey with makeup. The most effective is green-tinted concealer, as it's designed to negate red skin tones. First, use a thin brush to apply yellow corrector on the inside of the hickey, and use green corrector on the outside to negate the yellow tone. Then, apply a foundation (one a little lighter than your skin tone) directly on and all around the hickey so it's not obvious you’re concealing something. After that, apply some concealer if that hasn't done the trick.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_xcwh_06'/><br/>
<big>6　</big>Cover the hickey with clothing or hair. This is a great last-ditch effort, especially when it's cold. Try wearing a turtleneck, scarf, or collared shirt, jacket, or blouse (dress appropriately for the weather). You can also try accessorizing with a necklace to draw attention away from the side of your neck.
<p>　● You can alsoStyle your hair (if it's long enough) so it hangs over the hickey.</p>
<p>　● Wear a shirt that draws attention to your chest and away from your neck. Don't wear anything with elaborate designs around the neck area.</p>
<p>　● Obviously, wearing a turtleneck in the middle of the summer will only draw more attention to your look.</p>

<img src='training_xcwh_07'/><br/>
<big>7　</big>Apply arnica salve to the hickey. Arnica is an herbal salve that some claim helps reduce swelling and can minimize the appearance of a hickey. Just be aware that there is no scientific support for arnica reducing swelling. Some people claim witch hazel will also shorten hickey healing time.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_xcwh_08'/><br/>
<big>8　</big>Apply Vitamin K cream to the hickey. Vitamin K may help reabsorb the blood stuck near the surface of the skin that causes the appearance of a hickey (more specifically the redness or brownness).<br/><br/>

<img src='training_xcwh_09'/><br/>
<big>9　</big>Apply heat to a hickey that lasts more than a couple days. Saturate a washcloth in hot water, wring it out, and hold it to your skin for several minutes. Reheat the washcloth with more water as necessary. Alternatively, you can try a reusable heat patch from the pharmacy – it stays hot longer, it's easy to use and cheap.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_xcwh_10'/><br/>
<big>10　</big>Massage the area. This helps get blood circulation going and will help at the very least to lighten the damage. Gently place two fingers over the affected area and rub them in a circular pattern in one direction. After a minute, switch and rub your fingers in the other direction.<br/><br/>

<img src='training_xcwh_11'/><br/>
<big>11　</big>Wait it out. Hickeys will usually fade naturally in a couple of days to a week. There’s no sure way to get rid of one other than waiting, so be patient and try to minimize or hide its appearance as much as you can.<br/><br/>

<p>
<h1>Tips</h1>
　☞ Following the steps in How to Get Rid of Bruises may also help, since both hickeys and bruises are caused by pooled blood.<br/>
　☞ If someone notices your hickey, play it off. The excuse of the "curling iron burn" is common, but it won't work on a lot of people because a burn and a bruise look nothing alike to anyone who knows. Try a different excuse, one that would cause a bruise, like you got hit with a ping-pong ball or other projectile. People probably won’t believe you, but at least it’s plausible.<br/>
　☞ Eat strawberries. They contain saliycylic acid which is a blood thinner. It is a natural way to reduce swelling.<br/>
　☞ Applying too much pressure to the hickey will cause the blood to go away but can leave a lasting bruise. These bruises often have a greenish cast.<br/>
　☞ Never apply ice directly to a hickey. Wrap ice cubes in a towel to make a compress, and remove it if the cold becomes too painful. You can get frostbite if it’s too cold, or if you hold it on for too long.<br/>
　☞ If someone suggests a hickey "cure" that sounds dangerous or stupid, don't try it. Use common sense; a hickey really isn't a big deal.<br/>
</p>

<p>
<h1>Things You'll Need</h1>
　☞ Toothbrush<br/>
　☞ Eyeshadow or foundation a little lighter than your skin tone	<br/>
　☞ Concealer (preferably the green kind)<br/>
　☞ Ice pack (pre-frozen ice pack or ice cubes wrapped in a towel)<br/>
　☞ Concealing clothes<br/>
</p>
            ]]></text>
    </article>

													
<!--
<big>　</big>
<big>　</big><br/><br/>
<p>　● </p>
　☞ <br/>
<img src='training_xcwh_0'/><br/>
<big>　</big>
<p>　● </p>

	<article>
        <title></title>
        <text><![CDATA[]]></text>
    </article>
 -->    
</articles>